【豆豆影咖·点播影院】
嘿，我的钱包，他拿了我的钱包
Hey  My purse  He's got my purse
嘿，拦住他快点。
Hey, stop him   Come on.
谁去拦住他，他拿了我的钱包
Somebody stop him  He's got my purse
警察冻结
Police  Freeze
嘿别挡我的路
Hey  Stop  Out of my way
别挡我的路别挡我的路警察
Get out of my way  Out of my way  Police
移动
Move
你不会就这么下去了吧…
You did not just go down there...
什么他妈的
What the fuck
操的缘故。
Fuck sakes.
把你的手举起来
Get your fucking hands in the air
我不会再说一遍，混蛋
I ain't gonna say it again, motherfucker
他妈的。
Fuck.
你好,侦探Bozwick。
Hello, Detective Bozwick.
我想玩个游戏。没有
I want to play a game.  No
3号火车将在两分钟后到达。
The 3 train is arriving in two minutes.
这主要取决于你
It is up to you to decide
如果这是你的最后一站。
if this will be your final stop.
你做过很多次证人席，
You have taken the witness stand many times,
用你的谎言诬陷无辜的人，
and railroaded innocent people with your lies,
把他们送进监狱。
putting them away in jail.
今天，你将被钉上铁钉。
Today, it is you who will be railroaded.
你只有一次活下去的机会。
You have one chance to live.
从你的嘴里撕下你经常使用的舌头
Tear from your mouth the tongue that has so often been used
撒谎和欺骗。
to lie and to deceive.
信仰上的飞跃，你会活下去。
Take a leap of faith, and you will live.
只有你的体重会消失
Only your weight will rip away
你说谎的舌头，救了你。
your lying tongue and save you.
生或死，你自己选择。
Live or die, make your choice.
你在说什么?那部电影得了奖。
What you talking about  That movie won awards.
汤姆·汉克斯是个拉皮条的，
You know, Tom Hanks is a straight pimp, man,
但我不知道你今天能不能拍那部电影。
but I don't know if you could make that movie today.
你他妈在说什么
What the fuck you going on about
特殊需要的虐待。特殊需要
Special needs abuse. Special needs
什么，你醒了没醒
What, you woke now Not woke,
但你不能说"残疾"也不能说"弱智"
but you can't say "handicapped," you can't say "retarded."
你得说"特殊需要"我尽量尊重你。
You got to say "special needs," I'm trying to be respectful.
阿甘正传是有特殊需要的。
Forrest Gump was special needs, man.
那个女孩叫什么名字
What was the name of the girl
珍妮。珍妮。
Jenny.  Jenny.
他为珍妮做了一切。
He did everything for Jenny.
这混蛋干了些坏事。
This motherfucker did some shit.
他慢跑穿越了整个国家。
He jogged across the whole country.
他在乒乓球比赛中击败了中国。
He beat China in pingpong.
你知道那有多难
You know how fucking hard that shit is
他是一位战争英雄。
He was a war hero.
谁他妈比阿甘还好
Who the fuck is nicer than Forrest Gump
他最好的朋友
His best friend
一个黑人和一个没有腿的白人男孩。
was a nigga and a white boy with no legs.
他卖虾赚了10亿美元。
He made a billion dollars selling shrimp.
可她还是不肯上他。
And she still wouldn't fuck him.
嘿，他们终于在一起了。
Hey, eventually, they got together.
是的，在她得了艾滋病之后。
Yeah, after she got AIDS.
她一得了艾滋病就说"嘿福雷斯特"
As soon as she got AIDS, she's like, "Hey, Forrest..."
给我滚出去，伙计。
Get the fuck out of here, man.
让那个家伙得了艾滋病
Giving that guy AIDS
你在开玩笑吗是的。
Are you kidding me   Yeah.
狗屎的虐待。但他不明白。
That shit's abusive.  But he ain't get it.
我没看到续集。阿甘的2
I ain't see no sequel. Where's Gump 2
里科刚从电梯里出来。
Yo, Rico just got off the elevator.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
让我们这样做。
Let's do this.
趴下马上趴下
Get down  Get down right now
马上下来你知道这是什么
Get down right now  You know what this is
你知道这是什么
You know what this is
这就对了把一切都放下来吧
That's right  Put it all  Come on  Down
把这个袋子装满把它放进那个该死的袋子里
Fill up this bag  Put it in the motherfucking bag
来吧。
Come on.
你知道该怎么做，冷静
You know what to do   Chill
回来
Get back
我要那可卡因，我要那笔钱
I want that coke  I want that money
我想要一切
I want everything
大便。
Shit.
90秒，我们得走了
Ninety seconds, we gotta go
冻结的警察
Freeze  Police
举起手来，举起手来
Hands up  Get your hands up
从车里出来。给我滚…
Get out of the car. Get the fuck out of...
齐克是你吗
Zeke  Is that you
齐克
Zeke
你他妈有什么毛病
What the fuck is wrong with you
你做一个卧底行动…
You do an undercover op...
你不清理，就没有协调。
You don't clear it, there's no coordination.
我们是杀人,
We are Homicide,
但你却在酒店里抢劫毒贩。
but you're robbing drug dealers in a fucking hotel.
我接到了一打报警电话。
I had a dozen 911 calls come in.
如果有人被杀了怎么办
What if someone got killed
那伙人上周杀了四个人，我们抓到他们了。
That crew killed four people last week, and we got them.
如果我的身份没有暴露的话我们还能抓到更多的人。
And we could have got more of them if my cover wasn't blown.
去你的伪装，齐克
Fuck your cover, Zeke
你像往常一样一个人走了，没有后援，什么都没有。
You were off on your own, as usual, no backup, nothing.
没有后援，因为警察里没人
No backup, 'cause there's nobody on the force
我可以相信
I can fucking trust
从现在起，你要学会做一个有团队精神的人。
From now on, you're going to learn to be a team player.
你有搭档了。珍妮，让申克进来。
You're getting a partner. Jeannie, send Schenk in.
我看起来像他妈的牙买加保姆吗
Do I look like a fucking Jamaican nanny
我闻起来像肉酱和婴儿湿巾吗不是吗
Do I smell like jerk sauce and baby wipes  No
我不想要搭档
Me no want no partner
我才不要给什么破车当保姆。
I'm not babysitting some fucking rook.
是的,你是。
Yes, you are.
就因为你爸是他妈的马库斯·班克斯警长
Just because your dad was Chief fucking Marcus Banks
不代表你就能逃出来。
doesn't mean you get out of the shit.
别再提我父亲了，好吗
Stop making this about my father, okay
他走了，你现在是系主任了。
He's gone, you're the head of the department now.
是的。戏剧皇后。
Yeah. Drama queen.
齐克，都12年了
Zeke, it's been 12 years.
是的，12年。
Yes  Twelve fucking years.
十二年前，我告发了一个坏警察，
Twelve years ago, I turned in a dirty cop,
我因此得到一枚奖章。大不了他妈的
I get a medal for it. Big fucking deal
我还有一颗子弹
I also got a bullet,
我得在以后的职业生涯中小心翼翼
and I got to look over my back for the rest of my career.
闭嘴
Shut up
这里他妈的太热了
It is too fucking hot in here
让我听你胡扯。
for me to listen to this bullshit.
我有一股热浪。
I got a heat wave going on.
我们有轮流停电，
We got rolling blackouts,
这个城市疯了。停止
the city is nuts. Stop
你要见我，上尉
You wanted to see me, Captain
是的,请进。
Yeah, come in.
齐克，我想让你见见
Zeke, I want you to meet
训练中的警探威廉·申克。
Detective in training, William Schenk.
他是警校的尖子生，所以别搞砸了。
He was the top of his academy, so don't screw this up.
齐克会让你入门，教你入门。
Zeke is going to break you in, show you the ropes.
班克斯警探，很高兴…
Detective Banks, it's good to...
是的……
Yup...
走了。好吧。
Go.  Okay.
官哈里斯,103。
Officer Harris, 103.
琼斯中士，前台。
Sergeant Jones, front desk.
所以,嗯…你早上怎么喝咖啡
So, uh... How do you take your coffee in the morning
一个人。
Alone.
好吧。
Okay.
嘿，伙计，我懂了。
Hey, man, I get it.
我也不想和别的孩子困在一起。
I wouldn't want to be stuck with some random kid either.
你不想做我的搭档。
You don't want to be my partner.
你又不知道。
You don't know that.
这一切都是你爸爸造成的。
Your dad's the reason for all of this.
他就是我当初想做这件事的原因。
He's why I wanted to do this in the first place.
我也不是他。
And I'm not him.
准备好不被打动。
Prepare to be underwhelmed.
银行和Schenk……
Banks and Schenk...
有个流浪汉被3号火车撞了。你起来。
Some homeless guy got hit by the 3 train. You're up.
彼得森侦探,
Detective Peterson,
拿221。彼得森侦探,221年。
pick up 221. Detective Peterson, 221.
这是你
This is you
比警车还厉害。
Beats the squad car.
班克斯警探正在去1019的路上。
Detective Banks en route to that 1019.
是在街道的北面还是南面
Would that be north or south side of the street
向北。收到
Northbound. Copy that.
你在干什么?
What are you doing
哦，只是家人。
Oh, it's just family.
这是我妻子，艾玛，这是我儿子，查理。
This is my wife, Emma, this is my son, Charlie.
他们是可爱的。趁它还在的时候好好享受吧。
They're cute. Enjoy it while it lasts.
“虽然持续”
"While it lasts"
没有比新警探的妻子更幸福的事了，
Nothing happier than the wife of a new detective,
没有比这更愤怒的了
and nothing more angry
比十年后的那个婊子强多了。
than that same bitch 10 years later.
也许是因为你管她们叫贱人。
Maybe it's 'cause you call them bitches.
我是半个意大利人，相信我。
I'm halfItalian, trust me.
女人不喜欢你叫她们婊子…
Women do not like it when you call them bitches...
你在跟我说什么女人，
What are you telling me about women,
年轻的草泥马屎。
young motherfucker  Shit.
我只是对你说的，不是对女人说的。
I just said it to you, I didn't say it to a woman.
我不会当着他们的面说。我又不是太矮。
I don't say it to their face. It's not like I'm Too Short.
我们才刚认识，但是，你已经解雇我了，我很感激。
We just met, but, you know, you're firing already, and I appreciate it.
我是说，我想说的是，
I mean, all I'm saying is, you know,
大多数犯罪发生在周末，假期，
most crime happens on weekends, holidays,
所以你会认为嫁给警察的人
so you would think anybody married to a cop
会明白这一点。
would understand this.
但是没有。
But no.
总有一天，你老婆会生气的
One day, your wife will be angry
因为你不能去参加她姐姐的生日晚宴
'cause you couldn't go to her sister's birthday dinner.
你可以给一个女人600个星期二。
You can give a woman 600 Tuesdays.
这不值三个周六晚上。
It ain't worth three Saturday nights.
所以,嗯…我猜你离婚了。
So, uh... I'm guessing you're divorced.
离婚了，不，还没有。我要离婚了。
Divorced, no, not yet. I'm going through a divorce.
那会更糟糕。这有点像化疗。
That's even worse. It's kind of like chemo.
大便。对不起。
Shit. Sorry.
抱歉，我们是警察。这是我们选择的生活。
Sorry for what  We're cops. This is the life we choose.
最高的离婚率和自杀率。
Highest divorce rate, highest suicide rate.
家庭暴力发生率最高。
Highest rate of domestic violence.
你决定当警察的时候，
Yo, when you decided to become a cop,
你已经很自信了
you pretty much assured yourself
你会孤独终老。
you were gonna die alone.
我妻子和我，我们要做心理咨询。
My wife and I, we're doing this counseling.
她让我，呃，研究交流之类的。
She's got me, uh, working on, like, communication.
是啊，那很好。
Counseling  Yeah, that's nice.
是啊，我老婆上了辅导员。
Yeah, my wife fucked the counselor.
他妈的,真的
Fuck, really
是的。耶稣。
Yeah.  Jesus.
女人欺骗。
Women cheat, too.
这很伤我的心。该死，好疼。
It hurts. God damn it, it hurts.
女人也会出轨，但事实是这样的。
Women cheat, too, but here's what happens.
女人白天出轨。
Women cheat in the daytime.
你白天做了很多事都能逃脱惩罚。
You can get away with a lot of shit in the daytime.
这是正确的。你可以骑
That's right. You can ride
黄昏前有很多鸡巴。嗯。
a lot of dick before dusk.  Mmmhmm.
妈的，我才发现普拉提根本不存在。
Shit, man, I just found out Pilates doesn't even exist.
等,严重
Wait, seriously
艾玛喜欢普拉提。
Emma loves Pilates.
我相信她会的。我相信她会的。
I'm sure she does. I'm sure she does.
不过别担心。
But don't worry about it.
你会没事的。你会永远结婚。
You're gonna be fine. You gonna be married forever.
我们得到了什么
What do we got
你自己看。
See for yourself.
看你自己。
Watch yourself.
如果你要吐，就别在证据上吐。
If you're gonna throw up, don't do it on the evidence.
你在开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me
我从12岁起就一直梦想着这个。
I've been dreaming about this since I was 12 years old.
啊。
Ugh.
你可以在地铁上看到很多电视机
You see a lot of TV sets on the subway
所有东西都在这里。
You get everything down here.
该死的。哇。
Damn. Wow.
啊。
Ugh.
这个混蛋很难认出来。
This bum's gonna be tough to ID.
我不确定这是不是流浪汉。
I'm not too sure this is a bum.
我不知道有多少流浪汉想要加入。
I don't know a lot of bums trying to get their steps in.
不管是谁，已经结婚了…
Whoever this is, is married...
戴着Fitbit。
and wears a Fitbit.
这个包裹刚到。
This package just came in.
对我来说是的。
For me Yeah.
那是什么
What is that
“打我。”
"Play me."
好吧。哇,哇。你在干什么?
Okay.  Whoa, whoa. What are you doing
我可不想弄坏我的电脑。
Don't want to fuck up my computer.
你好,侦探银行。
Hello, Detective Banks.
我是来帮助改革警局的，
I'm here to help reform the Metro Police,
提醒他们记住他们对这座城市人民的誓言。
to remind them of their oath to the people of this city.
你局里的一名警官拒绝改过自新。
One officer from your station refused to be reformed.
他不会是最后一个玩我游戏的人。
He will not be the last to play my game.
如果那个螺旋是我想的那样…
If that spiral is what I think it is...
拼图
Jigsaw
等等，我以为竖锯杀手已经死了
Wait, I thought the Jigsaw killer was dead
但如果是另一个模仿者
Yeah, but if it's another copycat...
这将是一场糟糕的演出。
It's gonna be a shit show.
我认得那栋建筑。
I recognize that building.
这是法院。
It's the courthouse.
我们去看看。
Let's check it out.
你们在这里做什么
What are you guys doing here
我们觉得你们可能需要支援。
Well, we thought you boys might need some backup.
去你的，费奇，这不是你的案子。
Fuck you, Fitch, it's not your case.
哟,齐克。
Yo, Zeke.
这是什么
What do we got here
那是什么鬼东西
What the fuck is that
那是他妈的舌头吗
Is that a fucking tongue
他妈的狗屎。
Fucking shit.
453年……谁是453
453... Who's 453
圆了
Circle up
好吧，这是我们所知道的。
Okay, here's what we know.
牙科记录证实是博兹。
Dental records confirm it's Boz.
对不起,伙计们。
Sorry, guys.
但是，听着，我们得抓住那个干这事的混蛋。
But, look, we got to catch the son of a bitch that did this.
列车员说他没看到什么。
Train conductor says he didn't see much.
他说他看到博兹悬在空中
Says he saw Boz hanging in the air
就在他撞到挡风玻璃之前。
right before he hit the windshield.
他说他看到博兹的嘴在流血。
Says he thinks he saw Boz bleeding from the mouth badly.
这个包裹是由快递公司寄出的
The package was sent from a delivery service
在昂格林大道的门廊上捡到的。
that picked it up on a stoop on Anglin Drive.
那螺旋呢
What about the spirals
队长，很明显是拼图游戏的模仿者，
Hey, Cap, obviously it's a Jigsaw copycat,
这就是我们要集中精力的地方。
so that's where we got to concentrate our focus.
当然，费奇，但我希望你坚持确凿的证据。
Sure, Fitch, but I want you to stick with hard evidence.
克劳斯，联系联调局，了解他们的情况。
Kraus, contact the Feds, get anything they got.
文件，旧视频，任何东西。
Files, old videos, anything.
我们有街道图片吗
Do we have street images
我们正在查，但数字取证科
We're working on it, but Digital Forensics was
能在Fitbit上找到博兹的行踪。
able to map Boz's movement off the Fitbit.
最后登记的地方是斯图尔特角，
Last place it was registered was Stuart's Point,
在放烟花的时候打了时间戳。
timestamped during the fireworks.
得有人给他妻子卡拉打个电话，告诉她。
Someone needs to call Kara, his wife, let her know.
我已经给她打过电话了。
Yeah, I already called her.
你叫卡拉
You called Kara
是的。
Yeah.
你认识卡拉吗不。
Do you know Kara   No.
你真的跟她说了吗，还是发短信给她了
Did you actually talk to her, or did you text her
让我猜猜，你发了个表情。
Let me guess, you sent an emoji.
他们有死去丈夫的表情吗
Do they have a dead husband emoji
我跟她谈过了，混蛋。
I talked to her, asshole.
嘿。我们得在消息泄露给媒体前通知她。
Hey. We had to notify her before it leaked to the press.
好吧，奥布莱恩说得对…
Okay, O'Brien's got point...
字幕：南宫
这是我的。
This is mine.
我和车是第一个到现场的。
Me and the rook were first on scene.
银行……
Banks...
对不起，这不是规定吗
I'm sorry, isn't this protocol
现在你又成为团队的一员了，齐克
Now you're part of the team again, Zeke
去你妈的。
Fuck you.
不,去你妈的。
No, fuck you.
来吧,齐克。
Come on, Zeke.
当你们这些混蛋把我当狗屎对待的时候，
When all you motherfuckers were treating me like shit,
朝我后背开枪，
shooting me in my fucking back,
博兹是我的朋友
Boz was my friend
博兹和我的孩子玩。
Boz played with my kid.
我们去看了他妈的比赛。
We went to fucking games.
操我不，操你。
Fuck me  No, fuck you.
他妈的混蛋……
Fucking assholes...
齐克，齐克，停下
Zeke  Zeke, fucking stop
在这里现在
In here  Now
拉上拉链出去。
Zip up  Get out.
好吧,队长。
Okay, Captain.
该死，黑鬼，洗手。
Damn, nigga, wash your hands.
我知道你为什么想要这个。
I get why you want this.
博兹也是我的朋友，但你一个人做不到。
Boz was my friend, too, but you can't do this alone.
我需要整个部门通力合作。
I need the whole department on this, working together.
我不想一个人做，好吗
I'm not trying to do this alone, okay
博兹是我的家人。你得让我带队。
Boz is my family, man. You gotta let me take lead.
你得让我抓住这个混蛋。
You gotta let me catch this motherfucker.
好了，伙计们，计划有变。
All right, guys, we got a change of plans.
银行正处于领先地位。
Banks is taking lead.
听好了。
Listen up.
我知道你们有些人认为我是叛徒。
I know some of you guys think I'm a rat.
有些人认为我是告密者。
Some of you think I'm a snitch.
有些人很生气我上了你们的妈妈。
Some of you are mad I fucked your mother.
博兹最后一次露面
Boz was last seen
7月4日斯图尔特角的游行…
at the July 4th parade at Stuart's Point...
．..所以应该有很多监控录像，
...so there should be plenty of surveillance footage,
所以检查你的标签，Instagram…
so check your hashtags, Instagram...
嘿
Hey
现在我们这里有个警察死了，伙计们，他被残忍杀害了。
Now, we got a dead cop here, guys, who was brutally killed.
一个倒下的兄弟，舌头被拔掉了。
A fallen brother whose tongue was ripped out.
我们得把注意力集中在案子上，解决这个问题。
We need to focus on the case and solve this.
把录像拿给班克斯警探
So get the footage to Detective Banks
把你的私事放在一边。
and put your personal shit aside.
O ' brien,你很好
O'Brien, you good
没问题，上尉。
No problem here, Captain.
好。
Good.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
我们要去的地方
Yo, where we going
表达我们的敬意。穿上西装。
Pay our respects. Put on a suit.
齐克……
Zeke...
卡拉……
Kara...
没关系。
It's okay.
不管是谁干的，我一定会找到他们。
Whoever did this, I'm gonna find them.
我不明白……这是怎么发生的?
I don't understand... How did it happen
卡拉，你妈妈来电话了。
Kara, your mother's on the phone.
是的,好的。
Yeah, okay.
齐克。
Zeke.
丽莎。
Lisa.
你还好吧，我…我发短信给你。
You okay  I, uh... I texted you.
好的，我知道了。
Yeah, I got it.
是布莱恩
Is Brian here
不，我姐姐在看着他。
No, my sister's watching him.
你的妹妹……朗达可以见我儿子，而我不能
Your sister... So, Rhonda gets to see my son, but I don't
我们真的要在这里谈吗
Are we really gonna do this here
不。不是今天。
No. Not today.
嘿,我是威廉。停止。
Hey, I'm William.  Stop.
齐克的伴侣,是的…
Zeke's partner, yup...
我就在外面等着。我就在外面等着。
I'll wait outside. I'll wait outside.
杰米在邻居家。
KARA: Jamie's at the neighbor's.
我不知道该怎么跟他说他爸爸的事。
I don't know how I'm supposed to tell him what happened to his dad.
我无法想象你现在的感受。
I can't imagine what you're going through right now.
我知道现在不是时候，
I know this is a bad time,
但我得问你几个问题。
but I got to ask you a couple of questions.
在过去的几周里
In the last few weeks,
你注意到什么异常情况了吗
did you notice anything unusual
我是说，博兹有没有说什么，或者表现得很紧张
I mean, did Boz say anything, or act stressed out
他是个警察，齐克。
He was a cop, Zeke.
所以没什么不寻常的
So nothing out of the ordinary
不。
No.
有一样东西，一辆黑色越野车
There was one thing, there was a black SUV
上周的一个晚上停在外面。
parked outside one night last week.
你得到了成功
You get a make
路虎，凯雷德，林肯我不知道。
Range Rover, Escalade, Lincoln   I don't know.
我把这事告诉了博兹，他就出去了，
I told Boz about it and he went out,
他走了过来，我不知道，
and he walked up, and, I don't know,
接下来我只知道，他在里面对着一个人大喊大叫。
the next thing I know, he was yelling at somebody inside.
知道他们在喊什么吗
Any idea what they were yelling about
你听到什么了吗?
Did you hear anything
不。如果再让我看到，我就去查车牌号。
No. If I see it again, I'll get a license plate.
如果你不介意的话，能把他的设备给我吗
If you don't mind, could you get me his devices
我要看他的iPad，笔记本电脑。
I need to look at his iPad, laptop.
是的。谢谢你,卡拉。
Yeah.  Thanks, Kara.
不错的…我得走了，伙计们。好吧，注意安全。
Nice... I gotta go, guys. All right, be safe.
齐克。
Zeke.
他知道你是个好警察。
He knew you were a good cop.
你去找出是谁干的。
You find out who did this.
你拿枪指着你老爸
You pull a gun on your old man
你他妈疯了
You out of your fucking mind
我差点杀了你。
I could have killed you.
你在说什么我有枪。
What are you talking about  I got the gun.
我差点杀了你。
I could have killed you.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here
你忘了房东是谁了吗
Did you forget who the landlord is
是啊，但你无权这么做
Yeah, but that doesn't give you the right
想什么时候来就什么时候来。
to just walk in here anytime you want.
租房者有权利。
Renters got rights.
你开始付房租，你就能得到一些权利。
You start paying some rent, you can get some rights.
听说过博兹。你一切都好吧
Heard about Boz. You all right
不,爸爸,我…我是混乱的。
No, Dad, I'm... I'm fucked up.
很遗憾听到这个消息。我知道你们很亲密。
Sorry to hear that. I know how close you were.
山寨拼图。这可能很困难。
Jigsaw copycat.That could be difficult.
你在说什么?没事。
What are you saying   Nothing.
只是，你知道的，作为警探队长，
Just, you know, being lead detective,
很多责任。
a lot of responsibility.
你有意见吗
You got a problem with that
还是你只是害怕我会让你难堪
Or are you just scared I'm gonna embarrass you
看到了吗。
See  That right there.
这不关你的事。
This ain't about you.
你总是在说自己的坏话。
You always making shit about you.
这就是毁了你事业的东西
That's the shit that ruined your career
和你的婚姻。
and your marriage.
所以，现在你在给父亲的建议
So, now you're giving fatherly advice
你在说什么，威利斯
What you talkin' 'bout, Willis
爸爸。我们住在同一栋楼里。
Dad. We live in the same building.
那天我在外面看到你，
I saw you out front the other day,
你朝我点头，好像我们是商场里唯一的两个黑人。
you nodded at me like we were the only two black guys in the mall.
我们已经一年多没一起吃过饭了。
We haven't had a meal together in over a year.
还没吃饭呢
Haven't had a meal
你饿什么，黑鬼
What  Are you hungry, nigga
你他妈想去吃一块吗
You want to go get a fucking slice
我来告诉你。
Let me tell you something.
我父亲上班，回家。这是它。
My father went to work, came home. That was it.
好了，我要走了，孩子。
All right, I'm gonna get out of here, son.
我要去卡拉家，表达我的敬意。
I'm gonna go to Kara's, pay my respects.
你会没事的。
You're gonna be all right.
今晚你过来，我叫点吃的，我们再讨论一下这个案子。
Come over tonight, I'll order some food, we'll go over the case.
就因为你爸是他妈的马库斯·班克斯警长
Just because your dad was Chief fucking Marcus Banks...
别再提我父亲的事了。十二年前,
Stop making this about my father. Twelve years ago,
我告发了一个坏警察。
I turned in a dirty cop.
皮特·皮特
Pete  Pete
发生了什么事
What happened  What happened
他用枪指着我。
He pulled a gun on me.
目击者拿枪指着你
The witness pulled a gun on you
因为局里没有一个我能信任的人
Because there's nobody on the force I can fucking trust
我盯着这玩意看了五个小时。
I've been staring at this shit for five hours.
我看黄片的时间都没那么长。
I don't even look at porn that long.
好吧,我出去了。接下来是什么
Okay, I'm out. What's next
不如你去查查数字取证科
Well, why don't you check with Digital Forensics
看看博兹的通话记录里有没有一辆黑色越野车
and see if anybody in Boz's phone log has a black SUV
我手机没电了，你有充电器
My phone is dead, you got a charger
你手机没电了，你是什么，小女孩吗
Your phone's dead, what are you, a little girl
把你的手机借给我，闭嘴。
Let me borrow your phone, shut up.
好吧。
Okay.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
不要在看《暮光之城》时耗尽我的电池。
Don't drain my battery watching Twilight.
很高兴你加入我们。
Glad to see you joined us.
你认为这和约翰·克莱默有关
You think this is linked to John Kramer
我给联调局发了些照片，看看会发生什么。
I sent some pictures to the Feds, we'll see what happens.
我们的监控怎么样了
How are we doing on surveillance
拜托告诉我花在摄像头上的两千万给我们带来了什么
Please tell me the $20 million the city spent on cameras got us something
特鲁里街
Drury
是的…从这里到这里的街道摄像头
Yeah...Street cameras from here to here
已经通过了。
have already been scrubbed through.
面部识别没有任何结果。
Facial recognition came up with nothing.
这个角落里有两个摄像头坏了。
There were two cameras broken on this corner.
费奇和克劳斯现在就在那里。
Fitch and Kraus are there now to canvas it.
不。关闭。关闭。
No. Closed. Closed.
博兹。
There's Boz.
他在追谁
Who's that he's chasing
我认识那个人。
I know that guy.
本尼赖特兄弟。他是一个骗子。
Benny Wrights. He's a hustler.
严重的玩意儿。
Serious tweaker.
在12街的一家被烧毁的面包工厂里。
Flops in a burntout bread factory down on 12th.
对付一个叫皮皮兹的毒贩。
Deals with a pusher, street name Speez.
我们应该告诉齐克去他的。
Should we tell Zeke   Fuck him.
我负责这栋楼，你去找斯皮兹。
I'll take the building, you track down Speez.
老大，让我看看那边的枪。
Hey, boss, let me see that gun over there.
左边的那个。对，对，来吧，来吧。
The one on the left. Yeah, yeah, come on, come on.
我代表市警局，
On behalf of the Metro Police,
我要感谢你的慷慨。
I want to thank you for your generosity.
我还有事要做。我出去了。
I got shit to do. I'm out.
他的协议是什么
What's his deal
他是个不老实的混蛋。
He's a crooked piece of shit.
今晚就到此为止吧。你确定
Let's just call it a night.   You sure
是的。回家了。
Yeah. Go home.
去看你老婆，去看你孩子。
Go see your wife, go see your kid.
你儿子叫什么名字
What's your boy's name
查理。查理。
Charlie.  Charlie.
好吧，我把它放下，然后马上回来。
All right, I'll put him down and come right back.
不，不，不，我不会待在这里的。
No, no, no, I'm not going to be here.
和我爸一起吃晚饭，讨论一下这个案子。
Meeting my dad for dinner, gonna go over the case.
好吧。
Okay.
嘿,威廉。
Hey, William.
是的
Yeah
今天的工作做好。
Good work today.
谢谢你,小伙子。
Thanks, man.
明天见。是的。
See you tomorrow.  Yeah.
本尼
Benny
醒来,本尼。
Wake up, Benny.
起床啦，伙计。
Rise and shine, my man.
本尼,来吧。起床了。
Benny, come on. Get up.
快点，班尼，起来。
Come on, Benny, get up.
你一切都好吧
You all right
他妈的我。
Fuck me.
我是黛博拉·克劳斯，请留言。
This is Deborah Kraus, leave me a message.
克劳斯,打电话给我。
Kraus, call me.
请留言，我会给你回电。
leave a message and I'll get back to you.
帮助帮助我
Help  Help me
你好,侦探惠誉。
Hello, Detective Fitch.
我想玩个游戏。
I want to play a game.
嘿,齐克。威廉。
Hey, Zeke.  William.
你起来干什么
What are you doing up
我让你今晚休息的。
I told you to take the rest of the night off.
没事，查理在睡觉。
Uh, it's fine, Charlie's sleeping.
正在睡觉。
Was sleeping.
就在等艾玛回家，她要来个女生之夜。
Just waiting for Emma to get home, she's having a girl's night.
女孩晚上出去玩。好吧。
Girl's night out. Okay.
你最好小心点
You better be careful with that,
可能会是鸡巴之夜。
might be a dick night out.
就因为你要离婚
Just because you're getting a divorce,
这并不意味着其他人的婚姻也要结束。
it doesn't mean that everyone else's marriages have to end, too.
听起来你很忙啊。
Sounds like you got your hands full.
你想给我回电话吗
You want to call me back
不,这是好的,
Nah, it's okay,
我们sleeptraining。真是他妈的噩梦。
we're sleeptraining. It's a fucking nightmare.
看,男人,嗯…我知道你和博兹关系很好，
Look, man, um... I know you and Boz were close,
我不知道该怎么跟你说。
I don't know how to tell you this.
你有话要说，威廉，说吧。
You got something to say, William, say it.
我按你的要求查了所有的警局记录，
Well, I'm looking through all the Metro records like you asked,
博兹被指控在证人席上撒谎
and Boz was accused of lying on the stand more than anybody...
比他妈大得多。
by like a wide fucking margin.
耶稣。
Jesus.
法院……
The courthouse...
这就是为什么舌头会出现在法院。
That's why the tongue was at the courthouse.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you
你是马库斯·班克斯吗?
Are you Marcus Banks
不，我是他儿子。嗯,Terroni交付。
No, I'm his son.  Well, Terroni delivery.
哦,好的。
Oh, okay.
爸爸
Dad
爸爸，给你吃的。
Pop, got your food.
草泥马
Motherfucker
你他妈怎么能不先打给我
How the fuck could you not call me first
我试过了，但你没接。
I tried, but you didn't answer.
那你他妈干嘛不等我回你电话
Well, why didn't you wait for me to fucking call you back
因为你会劝我放弃的
'Cause you would have talked me out of it.
我说了实话。
I told the truth.
给我滚远点，齐克。
Get the fuck out of my face, Zeke.
我们能进入房间吗
Can we get the room
该死的。
God damn it.
我就知道我不该让他当警察。
I knew I should have never let him become a cop.
这事很快就会失控的。
This shit's gonna go sideways fast.
他告发了一个坏警察。皮特是个卑鄙小人。
He turned in a dirty cop. Pete was a scumbag.
媒体将把他报导为英雄。
Press will make him out to be a hero.
那其他警察呢
And what about the other cops
你觉得他们也会称他为英雄吗
You think they're gonna call him a hero, too
他做了正确的事。
He did the right thing.
你知道我要做多少内部损害控制
You know how much internal damage control I have to do
我们会处理它。
We'll handle it.
我们一直都是，哈
We always do, huh
首席银行，这里是WF行动新闻。
Chief Banks, WF Action News here.
你是在
Are you in
抱歉，但我觉得你的脸
Oh, I'm sorry, but I think your face
侵入我的财产。
was trespassing on my property.
有什么我可以帮你的吗
Is there something I can help you with
不。
No.
好吧。去你妈的。
All right. Fuck you very much.
齐克·班克斯警探。
For Detective Zeke Banks.
银行,传入的。
Banks, incoming.
在我的桌子上。现在。
On my desk. Right now.
快递员送来了。
A courier brought it.
我们把他关起来问话。
We're holding him for questioning.
你好,侦探银行。
Hello, Detective Banks.
有人提出拯救，但被拒绝了。
Salvation was offered, but it was declined.
这混蛋以为自己是竖锯。
This fucker thinks he's Jigsaw.
这次甚至得到了一个娃娃。
Even got a doll this time.
我对警局有意见，
I have a bone to pick with the police department,
如果你要指责别人…
and if you're going to point fingers...
12日街大桥。我知道那个地方。
12th Street Bridge. I know that place.
．..你们应该先把枪对准自己。
...you should start by pointing them at yourselves.
天啊，还有两个街区呢。
Geez, that's two blocks away.
在你坦白之前，会有更多的人死去。
Until you come clean, many more will die.
待回来。
Stay back.
保持锋利。
Stay sharp.
等等，伙计们。
Whoa, hold it there, guys.
真是个变态，伙计。
What a sick fuck, man.
什么他妈的
What the fuck
哦,不……
Oh, no...
全能的上帝。
God almighty.
982.
惠誉。
It's Fitch.
我是班克斯警探
This is Detective Banks
请求备份。
requesting backup.
我在德克尔街。请求的备份
I'm on Decker Street. Request backup
操他。在追求,
Fuck him. In pursuit,
要求备份
requesting backup
啊，操我操我。
Ah, fuck   Fuck me.
你会没事的，坚持住。
You're going to be okay, stay with me.
你很好，你会没事的。
You're good, you're gonna be okay.
你会没事的。
You're gonna be just fine.
齐克先生拜托，拜托
Zeke   Sir  Please, please
让我们做我们的工作，来吧。
Let us do our job, come on.
来吧，让我们做好本职工作，走吧。我们走吧。
Come on, let us do our jobs, let's go. Let's go.
你们都他妈去哪了
Where the fuck were all of you, huh
我儿子八分钟内叫了三次支援
My son called for backup three times in eight minutes
你们这些混蛋谁也不能来
and none of you motherfuckers could get here
任何人任何事
Nobody  Nothing
蟋蟀。好吧，这就是我要做的。
Crickets. All right, this is what I'm going to do.
我要打电话给调度中心
I'm going to call Dispatch
找出离我们最近的人，
and find out who was closest available,
等我找到了，我就拿走这把枪
and when I do, I'm going to take this gun
然后杀了那个混蛋。
and shoot that motherfucker.
我们清楚
We clear
费奇，是你
Fitch, it was you
你又在耍我儿子
You fucking with my son again
去你的，狗娘养的
God damn you, son of a bitch
我下车
Get off me
你完蛋了，混蛋，听到了吗
You're done, motherfucker, you hear me
你他妈的做的
You're fucking done
别让我再看到你。
Don't let me see your face again.
好吧,叫克劳斯,
All right，call Kraus,
找出费奇最后的位置。
find out Fitch's last location.
你好,侦探惠誉。
Hello, Detective Fitch.
我想玩个游戏。
I want to play a game.
正义的浪潮在你身边高涨。
The tide of justice is rising around you.
90秒后，水会上升
In 90 seconds, the water will rise
到铜线的高度，
to the height of the copper wires,
如果你还在水箱里，
and if you are still in the tank,
你会被电死的。
you will be electrocuted.
除非你做出牺牲来净化自己。
Unless you make the sacrifice that will cleanse you.
惠誉:神…哦,上帝…
FITCH: God... Oh, God...
你杀了一个人因为他侮辱了你。
You murdered a man because he insulted you.
把你的手
Put your hands
在我能看到的地方，混蛋。
where I can see them, motherfucker.
我说了把手放在我能看到的地方，先生。
I said put your hands where I can see them, sir.
你的手指扣动了扳机
Your finger pulled the trigger
这种情况不能再发生了。
and that cannot happen again.
生存很简单，但需要付出牺牲。
Survival is simple, but it comes with a sacrifice.
用嘴咬住这个装置，
Bite down on the device in your mouth,
哪一个能启动马达
which will start the motor
它会把你的手指撕裂…
that will rip your fingers away...
．..让你自由
...leaving you free
带着你的生命逃离。
to escape with your life.
但如果你不赶快行动，
But if you don't act quickly,
等着你的只有这个水坑。
all that awaits you is this watery tomb.
生或死，你自己选择。
Live or die, make your choice.
克劳斯，找到手指的那座桥有什么特别之处吗
Hey, Kraus, anything special about the bridge where we found the fingers
是啊，为什么是那座桥
Yeah, why that bridge
他就是在那里枪杀了吉米·林肯。
It was where he shot that kid, Jimmy Lincoln.
那你们是怎么发现这个地方的
Then how did you guys find out about this place
这个叫本尼·赖特的人
This guy, Benny Wrights,
博兹最后一次出现是在7月4日。
who Boz was last seen with on July 4th.
你怎么知道博兹最后和谁在一起
How do you know who Boz was last seen with
我们从斯图尔特角的一家当铺上取下来的。
We took it off a pawn shop feed in Stuart Point.
你却没告诉我。
And you didn't tell me.
这是谁干的
Who the fuck did this
一个对市警局有意见的人。
Somebody who has it out for the Metro PD.
或许只是为了费奇。
Or maybe just for Fitch.
你想说什么，德鲁里
You trying to say something, Drury
你知道我在说什么。
You know what I'm saying.
我怀疑你会为费奇流泪。
I doubt you'll be shedding tears for Fitch.
好了，来吧。来吧,齐克。
All right, come on. Come on, Zeke.
他妈的混蛋。
Fucking asshole.
好吧,忽略他。
Okay, ignore him.
你有什么发现吗?
Did you get anything
有一个名字。本尼赖特兄弟。最后一个和博兹在一起的人。
Got a name. Benny Wrights. Last guy Boz was seen with.
好吧，找到他，你只有几小时，而不是几天。
Okay, find him, and you got hours, not days.
本尼就是在这里买冰毒的。
And this is where Benny gets his meth.
你知道那是什么
You know what that is
这是测验吗?
Is this a test
只是问你个问题。呃，是个毒品窝点。
Just asking you a question.  Uh, it's a meth house.
你把钱放桶里，冰毒就来了。
You put the money in the bucket, the meth comes down.
有人看了《火线》
Oh, somebody watched The Wire.
这是新杰克城的鬼话。该死的。
This is some New Jack City shit. Goddamn.
我们不需要搜查令吗
Don't we need a warrant for this
你在说什么
What you talking about
齐克……
Zeke...
嘿，我的兄弟，我的兄弟。
Hey, my man, my man.
我和我的女人只是想要5分
Just trying to get a five, me and my lady
这是我们的结婚纪念日，我们想庆祝一下，
It's our anniversary, we're trying to celebrate,
尝试做一些特别的事情。
trying to do something special.
能给我5分吗这个iPad怎么样
Can I get a five  How about this iPad
上面什么都有。
It's got everything on it.
我有密码，有Netflix, Hulu，
I got passcodes, I got Netflix, Hulu,
优步餐厅，Postmates。很多食物，很多食物。
uh, Uber Eats, Postmates. Lots of food, lots of food.
让我看看……
Let me see that...
伙计，给我滚出去。
Yo, man, get the fuck out of here.
你看我他妈饿了吗
Do I look fucking hungry to you
哟，哟，它什么都有。但不合身。
Yo, yo, it got everything. It don't fit, though.
你为什么不下来
Why don't you come down
给我滚出去
Get the fuck out of here
你拿了钱就回来
Come back when you get some money
好吧,好吧。我需要钱，我需要钱。
Okay, okay. I need money, I need money.
不，不，不，等等，等等
No, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait
我有一些，我有一些钱。
I got some, I got some money.
我有些钱，等一下。
I got some money, hold up a second.
等一下，好吗
Hold up a second, all right
好了，传下去，宝贝。
All right, send it down, baby.
来吧，来吧，我们开始吧。
Come on, come on, let's do this.
等不及了
Can't wait
齐克，搞什么
Zeke, what the fuck
还有10秒钟，快点
It's got 10 seconds, come on
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
什么他妈的
What the fuck
让开别挡道。
Move   Get out of the way.
让开，让开警察
Out of my way, out of my way  Police
男:o
MAN: Fiveo
所有人，五个一动，一动，一动快点
Everybody, fiveo   Move, move, move  Come on
穿过。
Go  Coming through.
该死的警察，伙计。
MAN: Fucking cops, man.
哇,哇,哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa
狗屎带着你的狗
Shit  Get your dog
去你的，伙计。带上你的狗
MAN: Fuck you, man.  Get your fucking dog
现在嘿，友善点。
Now   Hey, be nice.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
神圣的他妈的狗屎。
Holy fucking shit.
这他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck's going on
回到里面。回到里面。
Back inside. Get back inside.
隐藏你的狗屎
Hide your shit
来吧
Come on
他妈的。操
Fuck. Fuck
我他妈的腿
My fucking leg
你为什么要把事情搞得这么复杂
Why do you make this shit so hard
如果我真的想搞砸呢
What if I really wanted to get fucked up
草泥马…
Motherfucker...
你得让顾客轻松点，讨厌鬼
You got to make it easy for the customer, skeeve
我他妈的腿
My fucking leg
这条腿糟透了。
That leg is fucked up.
哟，哟，哟，哟
Yo, yo, yo, yo
让我给奶奶拍张照片。
Let me get a shot for the Gram.
稍等一下。
Hold on for one second.
毒贩:这他妈是…等一下，等一下。
DRUG DEALER: What the fuck... Hold on, hold on.
我的男人。
My man.
好了，你想让我标记你
Here we go  You want me to tag you
他妈的……去你妈的。
Fuck... Fuck you.
我能标记你吗，狗娘养的操你…
Can I tag you, motherfucker   Fuck you...
你以前见过这个人
You see this man before
我什么都不会告诉你
I ain't telling you shit
为什么，因为你担心那块骨头会伸出你的腿吗
Why, 'cause you're worried about that bone sticking out your leg
你为什么不让我给它消毒
Why don't you let me sterilize it
不…不…没有操
No... No... No  Fuck
我是班尼，请停下
It's Benny  Stop, please
大家都认识那个该死的班尼·莱特
Everybody knows that motherfucker Benny Wrights
他是我最好的顾客之一。
He's one of my best customers, man.
你最后一次见他是什么时候
When was the last time you saw him
我已经两天没见过那婊子了。
I ain't seen the bitch in two days, man.
坊间传言那混蛋吸毒过量。
Word on the street is that motherfucker OD'd.
他妈的这金色飞贼。
Fuck this snitch.
操
Fuck
那是浪费时间。
Well, that was a waste of time.
我们知道本尼死了。
Well, we know Benny's dead.
冰毒不是那种需要休息的东西。
Meth isn't the type of thing you take a break from.
而且，你也看到那个装置了
Besides, you see that device
那不是蛀牙的人设计的。
That was not designed by anybody with rotten teeth.
你觉得这个竖锯角怎么样
What do you think about this whole Jigsaw angle
你认为那是，你怎么称呼的，那些门徒中的一个
You think it's a, whatdoyoucallthem, one of those disciples
约翰·克莱默的目标不是警察。
John Kramer didn't target cops.
不管是谁干的，都有另一个动机。
Whoever did this has another motive.
个人的东西。
Something personal.
他们不服从命令
And they're not following orders,
尤其是鬼魂的命令。
especially the orders of a ghost.
鬼,
Ghost or not,
有人在幕后操纵一切。
somebody's out there pulling all the strings.
你认为是这个人寄给你的
You think this guy sent you the boxes
因为你是负责这个案子的警探，
because you're the lead detective on the case,
或者因为你就是你
or because you're you
我不知道。
I don't know.
你有任何不是警察的敌人
Well, you got any enemies  That aren't cops
我不知道她为什么不再给我一次机会。
I don't know why she won't give me another chance.
我不知道，也许是因为你打了她
I don't know, maybe it's because you beat her
当你喝太多的时候。
when you drink too much.
你有没有想过
You ever think of that
这是一种严厉的爱。这家伙到底是谁
That's some tough love. Who the hell is this guy
Excop。搭档告发了他
Excop. Partner snitched on him,
被关了九年牢。
had to do nine years hard time.
体制把他赶走了，现在他在这里。
The system spit him out, now here he is.
嗨,皮特。
Hey, Pete.
齐克。
Zeke.
我没想到会在这见到他。
Last guy I expected to see here.
你想戒酒
You trying to get sober
酒精不是我的问题
Alcohol's not my problem.
玻璃和瓶子都能杀人。
The glass and the bottle can kill.
你好吗，皮特
How you doing, Pete
十八个月没喝酒，住在教堂地下室，
Eighteen months sober, living in a church basement,
谁还能要求别的呢
who could ask for anything more
这是谁
Who's this
侦探Schenk。我们在一起办案。
Detective Schenk. We're working a case together.
彼得:一起工作
PETE: Working together
别让他抓到你乱穿马路，
Don't let this guy catch you jaywalking,
否则他会在你背后捅一刀。
or he'll stab you right in the fucking back.
别忘了，皮特，你给了我那把刀。
Don't forget, Pete, you gave me the knife.
你说得对，是我干的。
You're right, I did.
你也看到了这个警察
And you witnessed this cop
把受害者从屋顶扔下去
throw the victim off a rooftop
你亲眼所见，我是说，亲眼所见
And you saw it, I mean, with your own eyes
你可以确定这个警察的身份
And you can positively ID this cop
他已经把脚踩在这个社区的脖子上太久了。
He's had his foot on the neck of this community for way too long.
我们不能这样。
We can't have this.
我会作证的，邓利维警官。我将这样做。
I'll testify, Officer Dunleavy. I'll do it.
皮特皮特发生了什么发生了什么
Pete  Pete  What happened  What happened
他用枪指着我。
He pulled a gun on me.
目击者拿枪指着你
The witness pulled a gun on you
我疯了很久，但现在我承担了责任。
I was mad for a long time, but now I take responsibility.
我就不该扣动扳机。
I should have never pulled the trigger.
那家伙有家庭。
The guy had a family.
那时候很疯狂，对吧
It was crazy back then, right
我们是在第8条下工作的。
We were working under Article 8.
我们失去了控制。
We were out of control.
警察被赋予了打击犯罪的自由裁量权。
Cops were given their own discretion to crack down on crime.
7月4日晚上9:30你在哪里。
Where were you July 4th at 9:30 p.m.
真的这就是你来这里的原因
Really  That's what you're here for
这就是我在这里的原因。
That's what I'm here for.
听着，有个人喝醉了去开会
Look, some guy came to a meeting drunk
想和赞助商打一架，所以我打了他。
and wanted to fight a sponsor, so I hit him.
把他打晕了。
Knocked him clean out.
不管怎样，警察来了。我还在缓刑期
Anyway, the cops came. I'm still on probation,
但幸运的是，是奥布莱恩。
but lucky for me, it was O'Brien.
他让整个事情顺其自然，因为，你知道…
He let the whole thing slide because, you know...
忠诚。
loyalty.
Loyalty.
照顾,皮特。
Take care, Pete.
上帝爱你，齐克。
God loves you, Zeke.
比你更多。
More than you.
真不敢相信那家伙以前是个警察。
Can't believe that guy used to be a cop.
他枪杀了一个无辜的人，但你背叛了他
He shot an innocent guy, but you turned on him
有个规矩，你最好学会怎么遵守，
There's a code, and you better learn how to follow it,
否则你这辈子就得小心翼翼了。
or you're going to spend the rest of your life watching your back.
公平点。
Fair point.
也许他们让我们成为搭档是件好事。
Maybe it's a good thing they made us partners.
留个口信。
Leave a message.
是的，爸爸，我在你的公寓。
Yeah, Dad, I'm at your apartment.
我昨晚在这里。
I was here last night.
你看起来不像是回家过。
It doesn't look like you've been home.
好吧，给我打电话。
All right, give me a call.
你已经接通了威廉
You've gotten through to William,
请在哔声后留言。
leave a message after the beep.
申克，现在是早上九点
Schenk, it's 9:00 a.m.,
你他妈的在哪儿给我打电话。
where the fuck are you  Give me a call.
珍妮:告诉我发生了什么，好吗
JEANNIE: Just tell me what happened, okay
嘿,嘿嘿
Hey  Hey  Hey
把盒子放在地上
Put the box on the ground
在地上举起手来举起手来
On the ground  Hands up  Hands up
趴在地上举起手来，举起手来
On the ground now  Hands up, hands up
不要动
Don't move
带他离开这里。
Get him out of here.
带他去拘留室。
Take him to holding.
抱歉，班克斯，他从我身边飞过。
I'm sorry, Banks, he blew right past me.
不可能，齐克，那个不一样。
No way, Zeke, that one is not the same.
我要打电话给拆弹小组。
I'm calling the bomb squad.
安琪，你是部门主管。
Angie, you're the head of the department.
两名警察死了，没时间了。
We got two dead cops, there's no time.
让所有人。
Get everybody out.
所有人出去，所有人出去
Everybody out  Everybody out
每一个人,去
Everybody, go
那是他妈的皮肤啊。
Is that fucking skin   Ugh.
"我惹到你了吗，班克斯警探
"Am I getting under your skin, Detective Banks
"小心点，当你在寻找更多的尸体时，
"Careful, while you're looking for more bodies to drop,
“我要取下你的头。”
"I'll take your head."
“我要你的头……”
"I'll take your head..."
“我是不是惹怒你了……
"Am I getting under your skin...
“我是不是惹怒你了……”
"Am I getting under your skin..."
…的家庭。这是我妻子艾玛
...family. This is my wife, Emma,
这是我儿子，查理。
this is my son, Charlie.
那是什么鬼东西
What the fuck is that
上尉，这下面有东西。
Captain, there's something under here.
康斯坦丁油漆。
Constantine Paints.
谢谢,是的。
Thanks, yeah.
跟我来。
Follow me.
奥布莱恩:你怎么知道这个地方
O'BRIEN: How do you know about this place
齐克，你怎么知道这个地方的
Zeke, how do you know about this place
我爸爸以前常带我来这里。
My dad used to take me here.
注意脚下，先生们。
Watch your step, gentlemen.
它并不总是肉店。
It wasn't always a butcher shop.
曾经是康斯坦丁火车。
Used to be Constantine Trains.
就像爱好商店。
Like a hobby shop.
哦，天啊。
O'BRIEN: Oh, my God.
任何东西
Anything
我们正在分析录音。
FORENSICS: Well, we're analyzing the tape recording.
你好,侦探Schenk,
Hello, Detective Schenk,
我想玩个游戏。
I want to play a game.
你是警察学院的班长。
You were head of your class at the Police Academy.
他显然被剥皮了。
He was obviously skinned...
后期。
postmortem.
你爸爸是我当初想这么做的原因。
Your dad's the reason I wanted to do this in the first place.
．..身体得分第一
...the body was scored first
要把它们切成更大的条状，
to remove the pieces in larger strips,
胳膊，脖子，他撕开皮肤的时候……
arms, neck, as he ripped the skin...
也许他们让我们成为搭档是件好事。
Maybe it's a good thing they made us partners.
即使是防御的伤口，
Even the defensive wounds,
他显然试图反击
he clearly tried to fight back,
这就解释了更深的伤口。
which explains the deeper gashes.
船长,在这里。
Captain, over here.
是针对警察的连环杀手吗
Is it a serial killer targeting cops
受害者在警察体内吗
Is the victim inside a policeman
无可奉告。哈特局长今晚会发表声明。
No comment. Commissioner Hart will make a statement tonight.
我们得尽量保持他的身份
We got to try to keep his identity
除非我告诉他妻子
out of the press until I tell his wife.
"我激怒你了吗，班克斯警探"
"Am I getting under your skin, Detective Banks "
嘿,O ' brien。
Hey, O'Brien.
是的,老板
Yeah, boss
你见过齐克
You seen Zeke
不，暂时不会。
No, not for a while.
好吧，我要去调查悬案。
Okay, I'm heading down to Cold Case.
复制,队长。
Copy that, Captain.
我需要所有可用单位
I need all available units,
警官在比曼街和第三大道交口受伤。
officer down 3rd and Beaman.
请在毕蔓街3号报告。
Please report, 3rd and Beaman.
我们得到了什么
What do we got
我在写罚单，一个戴着猪面具的人，
I was writing a ticket and some guy in a pig's mask,
他拿着刀向我冲过来。
he runs up on me with a knife.
他捅了你的胳膊，然后就走了
So, he stabs your arm and just takes off
我尽我所能击退他，而他…
I fought him off the best I could and he...
他跑开了。
He took off running.
他有理由攻击你吗
Is there any reason he would have to attack you
不。他只是想招惹警察。
No. He just wanted to mess with the cops.
"小心点，当你在寻找更多的尸体时，
"Careful, while you're looking for more bodies to drop,
“我要取下你的头。”
"I'll take your head."
安琪，你是部门主管。
Angie, you're the head of the department.
安琪……
Angie...
啊,操
Ah, fuck
安吉接
Angie  Pick up
这里是安琪·加尔扎上尉，
Hey, you've reached Captain Angie Garza,
请在提示音后留言。谢谢。
leave a message at the tone. Thanks.
安琪，去大办公室他来找你了。
Angie, get to the bullpen  He's coming for you.
他妈的。他妈的,他妈的,他妈的。
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck.
狗屎
Shit
嘿,嘿嘿
Hey  Hey  Hey
你好你好,狗屎
Hello  Hello  Shit
帮助
Help
你好,加萨船长。
Hello, Captain Garza.
我想玩个游戏。
I want to play a game.
你掩盖了你部门的腐败，
You have covered up corruption in your department,
从不为无辜的人冒险。
never sticking your neck out for the innocent.
掩盖真相的责任在你。
Now, the coverup will be on you.
几秒钟后，滚烫的蜡
In a few seconds, boiling hot wax
会从你上面的管子里出来。
will be coming out of the pipe above you.
唯一能让你不被窒息的方法
The only way to stop yourself from being suffocated
就是切断你的脊髓
is to sever your spinal cord
你的脖子下面有一把刀，
with the blade beneath your neck,
这样可以阻止蜡的流出。
which will stop the wax.
你不能一走了之
You cannot walk away,
但你可以活下来。
but you can survive.
生或死，你自己选择。
Live or die, make your choice.
去你妈的
Fuck you
安吉安吉
Angie  Angie
你他妈给我闪开
Get the fuck out of the way
(怎么没人接电话?
How come no one is answering the phone
一名警官被袭击了，这里一片混乱。
An officer was attacked, it's fucking chaos in here.
安吉安吉
Angie  Angie
安吉
Angie
齐克，怎么回事
Zeke, what's going on
他有她
He's got her
是谁让她
Who's got her
凶手抓住了安琪
The killer has Angie
我猜你没听到，凶手只是
I guess you didn't hear, the killer just
在比曼街和第三街交汇处袭击了一名警察。
attacked a cop at 3rd and Beaman.
那只是障眼法，好让我们离开警局。
That was just a diversion to get us out of the precinct.
她就在地下室里
She's down in the fucking basement
你找到安琪了吗
Did you find Angie
在地下室，在地下室
In the basement, in the basement
Angie加尔萨船长,
Captain Angie Garza,
给前台打电话。
call the front desk.
打开它
Open it
快点
Hurry up
安吉
Angie
打开它
Open it
好吧。
Okay.
狗屎
Shit
没事的，没事的。不会有事的。
It's okay, it's okay. It's gonna be fine.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
没关系。
It's okay.
没关系……哦……
It's okay... Oh...
锁定下来。
Lock it down.
你理解我
You understand me
封锁这里，不许任何人离开这个分局。
Lock it down, nobody gets out of this precinct.
我需要所有的监控录像
I need all the footage from the cameras
在证物室。
in the evidence room.
好了,这……
Okay, here...
这是电话打进来的时候
Here's when the call came in,
但在你进来之前什么都没有。
but then there's nothing until you come in.
看这里，从13:11跳到了13:24。故障
You see right there, it jumps from 13:11 to 13:24. Glitch
不，没有故障，因为，
No, there's no glitch, because look,
在第一个框架上，保险柜的门是开着的，
on the first frame, the safe door is open,
但到了下一个，它就关了。
but on the next, it's shut.
还少了13分钟。
There's 13 minutes missing.
拿到这段录像
Access to this footage,
是通过计算机系统吗
is that through the computer system
是的，我们只需要一个警徽号和密码。
Yeah, we just need a badge number and a password.
我不能告诉你是谁删了视频，
I can't tell you who deleted the video,
但我能查到过去一天登陆服务器的人
but I can access who logged into the server over the past day.
字幕：南宫
等待……213号警徽是谁
Wait... Who's badge number 213
皮特·邓利维，我的老搭档。
Pete Dunleavy, my old partner.
邓利维他不应该有权限。
Dunleavy  He shouldn't have access.
他有多久没工作了
How long's it been since he was even on the job
你去的地方
Where you going
去拜访皮特。
To pay Pete a visit.
齐克，他不是唯一一个
Zeke, he's not the only one
你父亲也有权限。
Your father had access, too.
申克尸体的位置
Location of Schenk's body,
你说那是你父亲小时候带你去的地方。
you said it was where your father took you as a kid.
你最后一次见到你父亲是什么时候
When was the last time you saw your father
今天早上。废话。
This morning.  Bullshit.
草泥马
Motherfucker
搞什么，齐克
What the fuck, Zeke
去你妈的,男人
Fuck you, man
去你妈的滚出去
Fuck you   Get the fuck out of here
把他弄出去操你你离得太近了
Get him out of here  Fuck you  You're too close
你太接近这事了，齐克。
You're too close to this thing, Zeke.
皮特
Pete
留个口信。
Leave a message.
爸爸，我给你打了三次电话
Dad, I've called you three times,
请给我回电话
please call me back
大家都在问问题，我不想再找借口了。
People are asking questions and I'm sick of making excuses.
你有话要对我说操
You got something to tell me  Fuck
你想玩游戏吗，混蛋
You wanna play games, motherfucker
好吧，我玩。
All right, I'll play.
你没事吧
You okay
嘿
Hey
帮助
Help
皮特
Pete
皮特,醒醒。
Pete, wake up.
皮特
Pete
什么齐克
What  Zeke
他妈的。
Fuck.
把我放下来，齐克。
Get me the fuck down, Zeke.
来吧
Come on
你黑了电脑。
You hacked the computer.
你删除了监控录像。
You erased the surveillance footage.
我不知道你在说什么，齐克。
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about, Zeke.
你杀了安琪什么
Did you kill Angie   What
是你杀了博兹吗
Did you kill Boz
你他妈在说什么
What the fuck are you talking about
是你杀了博兹吗
Did you kill Boz
博兹操…
Boz  Fuck...
你他妈是怎么回事，齐克
What the fuck is with you, Zeke
把我弄出去
Get me the fuck out of here
这是变态的报复吗，齐克
Is this some sick fucking revenge, Zeke
把我关进监狱还不够
Putting me in jail isn't enough, huh
把我弄出去
Get me the fuck out of here
你好,侦探银行。
Hello, Detective Banks.
我想玩个游戏。
I want to play a game.
当彼得·邓利维谋杀了一个无辜的人，
When Peter Dunleavy murdered an innocent man,
你的事业像玻璃一样被粉碎了。
your career was shattered like glass.
你能袖手旁观吗
Can you stand on the sidelines
正义最终得到伸张
while justice is finally served
有个办法可以救他，
There is a way to save him,
或者你可以把他关起来，然后扔掉钥匙。
or you can keep him locked up and throw away the key.
决定权在你。
The decision is yours.
"把钥匙扔掉"搞什么鬼
"Throw away the key," what the fuck
哈
Huh
快他妈把我弄出去。
Get me the fuck out of this thing.
齐克
Zeke
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
来吧,齐克。
Come on, Zeke.
把我弄出去，齐克
Get me the fuck out of here, Zeke
狗屎
Shit
齐克帮我
Zeke  Help me
齐克
Zeke
放我下来，快点，伙计。
Get me down, come on, man.
齐克
Zeke
．..或者你可以把他关起来
...or you can keep him locked up
把钥匙扔掉。
and throw away the key.
皮特
Pete
我来了,皮特
I'm coming, Pete
大便。
Shit.
他妈的。我抓住你了，抓住你了。
Fuck. I got you, I got you.
来吧,皮特。
Come on, Pete.
皮特
Pete
你这个不忠的混蛋。
You disloyal piece of shit.
从我们相遇的第一天起，我就对你忠心耿耿。
I've been loyal to you since the first day we met.
15年前。
Fifteen years ago.
你搭档杀了我父亲的那天。
The day your partner killed my father.
因此,查理,
So, Charlie,
你看到这个警察把受害者从屋顶扔下去，
you saw this cop throw the victim off a rooftop,
你可以确定这个警察的身份
and you can positively ID this cop
我会作证的，邓利维警官。
I'll testify, Officer Dunleavy.
我将这样做。
I'll do it.
皮特皮特发生了什么，发生了什么
Pete  Pete  What happened, what happened
他用枪指着我。
He pulled a gun on me.
目击者拿枪指着你
The witness pulled a gun on you
嘘。
Shh.
皮特杀了查理·埃默森。
Pete killed Charlie Emmerson.
你以为我会用真名吗
What  You thought I'd use my real name
你知道那有多难吗
Do you have any idea how hard it was
要进入这个部门，
to get placed in this department,
被分配做你的搭档
to get assigned to be your partner
那你的家人呢，你儿子呢
What about your family, what about your son
这是我儿子，查理。
This is my son, Charlie.
我没有儿子。
I don't have a son.
查理的睡觉…
Charlie's sleeping...
．..正在睡觉。
...was sleeping.
本尼·莱特斯带博兹下了地铁隧道……
After Benny Wrights led Boz down the subway tunnels...
我把我爸的名字纹在了他的手臂上。
I tattooed my dad's name on his arm.
我爸爸在哪儿?
Where is my father
你很快就能见到他了。
You'll see him soon.
我父亲到底在哪儿
Where the fuck is my father
我甚至都没叫他过来。你所做的。
I didn't even ask him to come down here. You did.
把你的手机借给我，闭嘴。
Let me borrow your phone, shut up.
好吧。
Okay.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
别看《暮光之城》把我的电池都耗光了。
And don't drain my battery watching Twilight.
他在哪里
Where is he
你不想听我的提议吗
Don't you want to hear my offer
我有选择吗
Do I have a choice
我想成为合伙人。
I want to be partners.
齐克，你对一个黑警采取了立场，
You took a stand, Zeke, against a dirty cop,
它给你带来了什么
and what did it get you
一辈子都在看着你，一个人工作。
A lifetime of watching your back, working alone.
接到每个流浪汉的电话
Getting the call for every homeless bum
结果发现他已经死了。
who turns up dead.
我是说，让我们面对现实吧，这些混蛋
I mean, let's be real, some of these motherfuckers
都是彻头彻尾的邪恶。
are straight up evil.
费奇不支持你…
Fitch not backing you up...
操他。
Fuck him.
他不会再犯同样的错误。
He won't repeat that mistake.
而博兹，总是在宣誓后撒谎……
And Boz, always lying under oath...
但是你，你不一样。
But you, you're different.
你地铁最好的。
You're Metro's finest.
这就是我想和你合作的原因。
That's why I want to team up with you on this.
你去找那些坏警察，剩下的交给我。
You find the dirty cops and I'll take care of the rest.
你想让我帮你杀警察
You want me to help you kill cops
不,操不。
No, fuck no.
只有坏的。
Just the bad ones.
约翰·克莱默是对的，螺旋。
John Kramer was right, the spiral.
它是变化、进化、进步的象征。
A symbol of change, evolution, progress.
但为什么仅限于个人
But why limit that to an individual
当你能把它应用到整个系统时
when you can apply it to a whole system
你因为做了正确的事而被枪击。
You got shot for doing the right thing.
但面对现实吧，这些警察
But let's face it, these cops
他们不会自己清理的。
They're not going to clean up on their own.
但我们在这里，
But we take a tongue here,
有几根骨头，他们就会过来。
a few bones there, they'll come around.
我们要修复一个坏掉的部门。好吧
We're going to fix a broken department. Okay
你和我。
You and me.
好吧。
Okay.
让我们做它。
Let's do it.
我想相信你。我做的事。
I want to trust you. I do.
我在。但是我爸爸自由了。
I'm in. But my dad goes free.
1秒。
One second.
911请说明你的紧急情况
911, please state your emergency.
你好，我在旧肥皂厂
Hello, uh, I'm at the old soap factory
马迪根巷。
on Madigan Lane.
有个持枪的疯子，
There's a crazy guy with a gun,
他到处开枪。请快一点
he's firing it everywhere. Please hurry
那他妈的是什么
What the fuck was that
你最好快点，齐克，特警马上就到。
You better hurry, Zeke, SWAT's on the way.
听着，我想相信你，真的。
Look, I want to believe you, I do.
我想相信你。
I want to trust you.
拿着这个，你会需要的。
Take this, you'll need it.
来吧。
Come on.
我们去看你爸爸吧。
Let's go see your dad.
是时候做最后的测试了。
It's time for your final test.
爸爸。
Dad.
以西结。
Ezekiel.
该死把他放下来
Oh, shit  Get him down
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
我抓住你了，爸爸。
I got you, Dad.
齐克。帮助我,儿子。
Zeke. Help me, son.
别担心，别担心。
Don't worry, don't worry.
我不会让你死的。我要把你弄下来。
I'm not going to let you die. I will get you down.
没事的，坚持住。
It's all right, just hold on.
马上杀了这个混蛋。
Shoot this motherfucker right now.
把他弄下来快把他弄下来
Get him down  Get him down now
我以为我们是搭档。
I thought we were partners.
你要开枪了，齐克
You going to shoot me, Zeke
用你的一颗子弹
With your one bullet
坏主意。
Bad idea.
你爸爸会死的。
It kills your dad.
顺便说一句，他朝我开了一枪。
He took a shot at me, by the way.
错过了。
Missed.
我浪费了四个。
I wasted four.
也就是说你只剩一枪了，齐克。
That means you got one shot left, Zeke.
好了，警察来了。我们还有4分钟。
All right, cops are here. That gives us four minutes.
你知道人体内有1。5加仑的血吗，齐克
Do you know there's 1.5 gallons of blood in the human body, Zeke
以你老爸失血过多的速度，
At the rate your old man is bleeding out,
再过三分钟，罐子就满了
in just three minutes, those jars will be full
你爸爸会死的。
and your dad will be dead.
唯一能让他自由的东西
The only thing that can set him free
你枪里的子弹是对着那个目标开的吗。
is the bullet in your gun fired at that target.
不管怎样，我有个万无一失的办法离开这里。
Either way, I've got a foolproof way out of here.
你不是拼图。
You're not Jigsaw.
这是游戏。
That's the game.
杀了我，你们俩都会输。
Shoot me and you both lose.
射中目标，我们都赢。
Shoot the target and we both win.
你想玩吗
You want to play
我要死了，齐克，结束这一切吧。
I'm dying, Zeke, end it now.
在这个走廊。
In this corridor.
罗杰。西南入口。
Roger that. Southwest entrance.
从南门进去。
Going through the south door.
没有在这里。继续前进。
Nothing here. Keep moving.
我需要你们所有人。
I need you all in.
邓利维毁了我们俩的生活
Dunleavy ruined both our lives
你还想帮那个混蛋
and you tried to help that piece of shit
齐克皮特
Zeke   Pete
你考试没及格。
You failed that test.
现在我需要你选择和谁在一起。
Now I need you to choose who you're really with.
那个败坏了警队的人
The man who corrupted the force,
或者那个想要拯救它的人。
or the one who's trying to save it.
你想告诉他吗，队长
You want to tell him, Chief
告诉我
Tell me what
告诉他你根据第8条做了什么。
Tell him about all the fucking shit you did under Article 8.
他在说什么
What's he talking about
时间不多了。他在说什么
Time's running out.  What's he talking about
公民死亡。
Citizens were dying.
我们做了必须做的来清理街道。
We did what we had to to clean up the streets.
皮特:那时候很疯狂，对吧
PETE: It was crazy back then, right
我们是根据第8条工作的，
We were working under Article 8,
我们失去了控制。
we were out of control.
谋杀率下降了。
Murder rate went way down.
这是他妈的扯淡。
That's fucking bullshit.
人们又感到安全了。
People felt safe again.
警察越来越脏，街道也越来越干净。
The streets got cleaner because the cops got dirtier.
顺便说一句，你爸监督了整件事。
Your dad oversaw the whole thing, by the way.
无辜的人被枪杀，都是为了伸张正义。
Innocent people getting shot, all in the name of justice.
第8条是最腐败的一条
Article 8 was one of the most corrupt
历史上的警察政策，
police policies in history,
猜猜谁是你爸爸的得力助手
and guess who was your dad's righthand man
抱歉，或者我应该说女人，一直都是
Sorry, or should I say woman, the whole time
我们会处理它。我们一直都是，哈
We'll handle it. We always do, huh
安吉
Angie
这是安琪。
It was Angie.
我的意思是，这不是一个巨大的惊喜。
I mean, not a massive surprise.
你觉得是因为她的好名声
You think it was her stellar reputation
让她在35岁时就有了辖区拜托。
that got her a precinct at age 35  Come on.
杀了这混蛋，以西结。现在。
Shoot this piece of shit, Ezekiel. Now.
没错，因为那是警察的职责。
Yeah, that's right, because that's what cops do.
先开枪，再问问题。
Shoot first, ask questions later.
你看着我父亲死去而我想救你。
You watched my father die and I'm trying to save yours.
如果我们要信任彼此，
If we're going to trust each other,
我需要你这么做。
I need you to do this.
以西结…
Ezekiel...
你一直做的是对的，现在就做吧。
You've always done the right thing, do it now.
这混蛋在杀警察。
This piece of shit is killing cops.
你仍然需要做出决定
You still need to decide,
你可以开枪打我，或者…
you can shoot me, or...
或者你可以救你爸爸。
Or you can save your dad.
时钟的滴答声,男人。
Clock's ticking, man.
觉得快。
Think fast.
骑兵的到来。
Cavalry's coming.
但没来得及帮你老爸的忙。
But not in time to do any favors for your old man.
只有你能做到。
Only you can do that.
爸爸的爸爸
Dad  Dad
开火
Shots fired
齐克……齐克。
Zeke... Zeke.
会没事的。
It's going to be okay.
他走了。
He's getting away.
别让他跑了。
Don't let him get away.
去……去
Go... Go
停止。不要进来。
Stop. Don't come in.
不要进来。
Don't come in.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
不管是谁干的，都有别的动机，私人的动机。
Whoever did this has another motive, something personal.
这是谁……
Whoever did this...
．..他们在幕后操纵一切。
...they're pulling all the strings.
这一切都是你爸爸造成的。
Your dad is the reason for all of this.
他就是我当初想做这件事的原因。
He's why I wanted to do this in the first place.
我从12岁起就一直梦想着这个。
I've been dreaming about this since I was 12 years old.
这他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on
走,走,走
Go, go, go
趴下马上趴下
Get down  Get down now
工作人员2:让我看看你的手
OFFICER 2: Let me see your hands
不，不，不，停下
No  No, no, stop
没有神
No  God
冻结,不
Freeze  No, no
没有
No
放下
Put it down
降低你的武器
Lower your weapon
火
Fire
不
No
【豆豆影咖·点播影院】